（北蒙古）
Get off the babysitter。Daddy's home.
打发保姆，爸爸回家了
What is an Angel doing so far from Heaven？
为什么天使要远离天堂？
I'm no Angel.
我不是那种天使
This is hostel，yeah？
这里是民宿，对吧？
I'm good at the bull，no？
我很会骑公牛，对吧？
（雷·卡特，美国执法官）
Marshal Ray Carter？I'm Alex Munday。I'll be your rescuer today.
雷·卡特执法官，我是艾丽斯·蒙戴 今天我是来救你的
I didn't think you'd find me。How many men do you have？
我以为你们找不到我了 你们一共派几个人过来？
I've got two girlfriends in the bar.
我的两个姐妹淘在酒吧里
They have 50 armed men.
他们有五十个大男人戴着枪
I know。It hardly seems fair。Come on.
我知道，人生本来就不公平，来吧
- What is it？- My ribs.
- 怎么了？ - 我的肋骨
Dylan？Dylan，we need to get out of here.
黛伦，我们得离开这里
I'm on top of it.
我正在处理
- They got my ring。- I'm sure your wife will understand.
- 他们拿走我的戒指 - 我相信你太太会谅解的
Kill them！
杀了他们
Kill them all！
干掉她！
Plan B.
B计划
Just once，I'd like to walk out of a bar.
只要一次就好，我想走着离开酒吧
Let's go！
走吧
Now！
快点
- Get in！- You got him？
- 上去 - 你扶好他了吗？
Dylan！
黛伦
Go for it！
快点
- Dylan！- I'm trying！
- 黛伦 - 我在快了
I'm afraid I underestimated you guys.
恐怕我低估了你们的能耐
Yeah.
对
That happens a lot.
常有人那么说
It was three girls！
三个女孩子
Three crazy beautiful girls.
三个不要命的漂亮女孩子
But we have the ring.
把人带走了
I always knew this day would come…
我就知道会有今天
Let's go to plan B.
咱们按B计划行动
Once upon a time，there were three very different little girls.
很久很久以前 有三个与众不同的小女孩
（娜塔丽）
（艾丽斯）
Come on，Alex。This is the last pass。You can do it！
加油，艾丽斯，这是最后一次 你可以的
Harder！Harder！Harder！
加油
（黛伦）
I want you！I want you now！
我要单挑你，放马过来
Who grew up to be three very different women.
长大后变成三个与众不同的女人
No.
不
Okay.
好吧
You，hot water.
你去拿热水
Here it goes。Here it goes.
它出来了
There we go.
好了
Now they work for me。My name is Charlie.
现在她们为我工作，我是查理
《霹雳娇娃2》
（威廉·罗斯·贝利，司法部）
Perimeter secure。We're ready for takeoff.
全区封锁，准备起飞
Well done，Agent McDowell.
做得好，麦唐威探员
Hey，check this out.
快来看
Our first piece of mail.
我们的第一封信
- Your 10-year high-school reunion。- It'll be a fun night，Nat.
- 你的十周年高中同学会 - 一定会很好玩的，小娜
- Isn't that cool？- It's great.
- 那真的很酷吧？ - 太棒了
I still can't believe Nat and Pete are moving in together.
我还是不敢相信 小娜跟彼特居然住到一起了
- Our little Angel's growing up。- It's wild that Natalie owns property.
- 我们的小娇娃长大了 - 这太扯了，娜塔丽有车子
The most expensive thing I own are these boots.
我最值钱的财产是这双靴子
- Excuse me。Those are my boots。- Whatever。My point is…
- 对不起，那是我的靴子 - 随便，我的重点是…
I forgot my point.
我忘了重点是什么
You're broke，horny and wearing my boots.
你破产、色欲薰心、穿着我的靴子
Thank you.
谢谢
So you thought you could escape my fortress.
你以为你能逃出我的堡垒
Not so fast.
别高兴得太早
- Oh，my God！Jason。- Surprise.
- 天啊，杰森 - 大惊喜
- Are you okay？- Yeah.
- 你没事吧？ - 没事
That was fun.
那真的很好玩
Fun。Yeah.
很好玩，对
- What are you doing here？- I miss you。Look…
- 你来这里做什么？ - 我很想你，听着
What are you doing later，after this？Later on？
这里弄好后，你要做什么？ 我是说晚一点？
Jason，I thought we were on a time-out.
杰森，我们说好要冷静一下
What？We can't fool around at all？
什么？我们连玩玩都不行吗？
Hey，Jason。I didn't think you'd make it.
杰森，我以为你不会来了
Yeah，the photo shoot ran late。Plus，I wanted to miss all the heavy stuff.
对，拍照活动拖蛮久的 而且我想逃避帮忙搬重物的工作
Hey，Jason.
杰森
- How's the sequel going？- Great.
- 续集拍得如何？ - 很顺利
We had，like，13 writers，so it should be pretty good.
我们找来13位编剧 应该会很不错
- I loved the first one。- Yeah，it was great.
- 我喜欢第一部 - 对，真的很精彩
Sorry。We got a great title for this one：Maximum Extreme-2.
抱歉，这一部的片名取好了 《极限2》
The premiere's Friday，so I brought you tickets.
首映典礼在星期五 我帮你们准备好门票了
I love tickets！
我喜欢门票
- Hello？- Yeah？
- 喂 - 怎么了？
- Be right in。- Thanks.
- 马上到 - 谢谢
Sorry.
抱歉
- Thanks for helping out，Jason。- Yeah，yeah.
- 谢谢你来帮忙，杰森 - 对
Charlie.
查理
（查尔斯·汤森私家侦探社）
Bosley！
波西
What's happening，Angels？How y'all doing？
怎么样？娇娃们，你们还好吧？
Hey，Bos.
老波
Look here。I see my brother ain't checked the books in a while.
听着，我发现我兄弟有阵子没对帐
We have a book？
我们有帐本吗？
Look here，lovelies，I only been here a few days，but will you explain…
听着，美女们，我才来上班几天 你们能解释一下
…what the hell is this？
这是什么东西吗？
Now，what？
搞什么？
Careful with that，Bos.
小心点，老波
I'm all right.
我没事
And I also see y'all being played。Five G's for a Kevlar vest？
我还发现你们被骗了 防弹背心要五千块？
- We need those。- They're made especially for us.
- 我们需要那个 - 那是专门为我们订做的
What？You all fine，but you crazy.
什么？你们很漂亮，但你们疯了
What？
什么？
Bosley，come here.
波西，过来
- Have a seat，Bos。- Okay.
- 坐吧，老波 - 好的
- Bos。- What？
- 老波 - 什么？
B.
波
Your brother didn't sweat the details.
你兄弟没跟你解释清楚
- We do what it takes。- Right.
- 我们得做该做的事 - 对
So，what does a Bosley do around here？
在这里波西该做什么？
- He does the most important job of all。- What's that？
- 他做最重要的工作 - 什么工作？
He connects us with Charlie.
他帮我们跟查理联络
Okay。All right。All right.
好吧
- Good morning，Angels。- Good morning，Charlie.
- 早安，娇娃们 - 早安，查理
Bosley，I hope the Angels aren't being too rough on you.
波西，希望娇娃们没有为难你
Man，please。I date fat women。What are you talking about？
兄弟，拜托，我跟胖女人交往 你在胡说什么？
Great work in Mongolia，Angels…
蒙古的任务很成功，娇娃们
…but I'm afraid the case has taken a new turn.
恐怕案子有新发展
Goddamn！What the f… Look… Look…
该死，搞什么？快点看
I know where I'm watching the game at tonight。Look at that.
我知道今晚该去哪里看球赛 看看那玩意
Angels，I'd like to introduce Roger Wixon，senior director of the FBI.
娇娃们，我要跟你们介绍 罗杰·威克森，联邦调查局资深主任
- Pleasure to meet you。- Pleasure.
- 幸会 - 非常荣幸
- Hi。- Hello.
- 嗨 - 哈喽
Over the years，the Townsend Agency…
多年来汤森侦探社
…has worked on projects for the bureau…
为联邦调查局执行计划
…but never one with so many innocent lives at stake.
但内容不曾涉及众多无辜性命
Hey，I'm busy watching that doggone screen.
我正忙着看超大屏幕
Good job，Bos.
做得好，老波
Angels，you're aware of the Federal Witness Protection Program.
娇娃们，你们都知道 联邦证人保护计划
People who testify against major crime figures…
作证指控重大罪犯的人
…are relocated and given new identities.
必须搬家，以新身分过生活
The identities of these witnesses are protected by a program called HALO：
这些证人的身分受到幻影计划保护
Hidden Alias List Operation.
机密化名清单行动的昵称
The list is encrypted on two titanium rings.
清单经过加密 存放在两枚钦制戒指里
The data on each ring is indecipherable on its own…
每枚戒指的资料无法独自加以解读
…but when they are read together，their codes unlock each other.
只要将两份资料放在一起 它们会各自为彼此解密
Who wears the rings？
戒指在谁手上？
The head of the U.S。Marshal Service was wearing one.
一枚由美国执法局局长保护
- Ray Carter。- Good morning.
- 雷·卡特 - 早安
- Hey，how are you feeling？- Couple of fractured ribs，but I'll live.
- 你还好吧？ - 肋骨断了几根，我没事
Who wears the other ring？
另一枚戒指在手上？
The head of security for the Justice Department，William Rose Bailey.
司法部安全单位负责人 威廉·罗斯·贝利
Unfortunately，he was killed this morning.
不幸的是今天早上他遇害身亡
- Now both rings are in the open。- So the list is out.
- 现在两枚戒指下落不明 - 名单已经外流
Someone's contacted the major crime families offering to sell the list.
有人跟大型黑道组织兜售清单
（安东尼奥尼黑帮家族）
（迪亚伯洛集团）
（田中组）
（欧葛莱帝帮）
One of our protected witness，Alan Caufield…
一名受保护证人，亚伦·考菲德
…was found dead at home in the Valley.
被发现陈尸在谷区家中
Angels，we need to get the HALO rings back before the list is sold.
娇娃们，我们得在清单被卖掉前 将幻影戒指找回来
- We'll start at the Caufield house。- See if that leads us to HALO.
- 我们得在考菲德家找起 - 说不定那能带我们找到幻影戒指
Hey，Charlie，we could really use Bosley's help on this one.
查理，这次我们真的需要波西帮忙
- Get to drive the racecar？- Not today.
- 我可以开赛车？ - 今天不行
- Blow up a castle？- Not yet，Bos.
- 炸掉城堡？ - 还不行，老波
Well，what do y'all need me to do？
你们要我做什么？
- Read some body language。- Hell，yeah.
- 解读身体语言 - 该死，太棒了
（搜证专家）
（犯罪现场摄影师）
（犯罪现场鉴识小组主管）
（法医）
I'm not going nowhere near no dead body.
我绝对不要碰尸体
Freeze，ladies。If you're not a dead body，other side of the ropes.
不要动，美女们，不是尸体的人 请站在管制区外
We got a serious situation here。My men have the area secure.
事情大条了，我的人已经封锁全区
I have to ask you to evacuate immediately.
我得请你们立刻撤离
We got a 211，a 183，believe it or not，we got an 11-350，and it ain't pretty.
我们有211、183状况 还有11350，大事真的不妙
An 11-350？You found an illegal chinchilla ranch on the premises？
11350，你们在附近 发现非法龙猫牧场？
It's a chinchilla farm.
是龙猫农场
But you're good.
你真的很厉害
Negatory to orders to relinquish locality.
当地警方拒绝交出管辖权
Circumspect to your observation…
在你的严密监视下
…we'll proceed to the interior of the dwelling with your accompaniment.
我们愿意接受你的陪同 到屋里搜证
Well，I do not copy。Repeat，do not copy。I'll have to ask my sergeant.
我不接受，重复 我不接受，我得请示我的长官
Your sergeant is here.
你的长官就在这里
Hands off.
闪开
If you had your game faces on at the academy，you ought to figure this out.
如果你在警校时用功一点 你应该知道这是怎么一回事
Simple cafe coronary。Freak show choked to death.
普通的冠状动脉问题 这家伙是噎死的
Questions？
有问题吗？
Examination of soft palate reveals porcine byproduct…
检查过软上颔后发现猪肉副产品
…lodged in vestibule.
卡在喉咙
Okay，let's do this。Come on，baby.
好吧，就这么办，来吧，宝贝
Caufield shows no signs of trauma to the larynx.
考菲德的喉咙没有受伤
His struggle pattern indicates that he didn't choke.
打斗模式证明他不是噎死
He was smothered.
他是被闷死
Ladies，we got some carnauba residue.
女士们，我们发现巴西棕搁残余物
Pineapple.
菠萝
Oh，it's Sex Wax。Best for your stick.
防滑板，可以让你顺一点
Pardon me？
你说什么？
- The killer's a surfer。- How do you know？
- 凶手是冲浪手 - 你怎么知道？
He used the credit card he uses to scrape wax off his board…
他用刮掉冲浪板蜡的信用卡
…to gain entry into the house.
撬开门闯进屋里
Thrasher scumbag surfers.
天杀的冲浪手
Freeze！
不要动
I found a foreign print。He was wearing reissued 1989 Air Jordans.
我发现陌生脚印 他穿再版1989年飞人乔丹鞋
A limited promotional version sold…
限量宣传版
…only at the Foot Locker in Fontana，in the summer of 2002.
只有2002年夏天 在芳塔纳的球鞋专卖店有出售
There's a discrepancy in weight distribution…
左右两边
…between the left and right sides.
重心分布不平均
An anterior cruciate ligament that was repaired in the last year.
去年修复过后十字韧带
All right，who did it？
好吧，这是谁干的？
A killer with a scar on his knee who surfs.
凶手是膝盖有伤疤的冲浪手
Did he stink？
他很臭吗？
There's a hurricane off Baja。That means good swells for south beaches.
巴哈外海有飓风来袭 那代表南部海滩应该有大浪
Was there a lot of blood？
有很多血吗？
Offshore winds，Third Point。Malibu's pumping.
外海三级风，马里布是好地点
- Alex，surfboards are at your house。- Share it with me，Angels.
- 艾丽斯，冲浪板在你家 - 快告诉我，娇娃们
Freeze！
不要动
Daddy？Daddy！
爸爸
Darling！I was meeting your mother in Bali，and they canceled the flight.
亲爱的，我本来要到巴厘岛找你妈 结果班机被取消了
Some sort of monsoon。So how is my favorite little ferret？
是季风雨的关系 我最心爱的小宝贝还好吧？
Do the face.
装一下鬼脸
No，come on。Do it properly.
不，来吧，好好做一次
That is so cute。I do the whiskers with my dad.
那真的好可爱 我也会装鬼脸给我爸看
Mr。Munday，it is such a pleasure to finally meet you.
蒙戴先生，很荣幸终于见到你了
I'm Dylan.
我是黛伦
That's Natalie.
她是娜塔丽
I assure you，none of the stories are true.
我跟你保证那些故事都不是真的
Well，some of them are.
有些是真的
So you work with Alex at the hospital？
你们跟艾丽斯是医院同事？
Yes！Natalie works in the psychiatric ward…
对，娜塔丽在精神科病房工作
…and Dylan is the head of gynecology.
黛伦是妇产科负责人
Really？
真的吗？
- So young。- I know.
- 真是青年才俊 - 我知道
We were just on our way out。We have a major procedure coming up，so…
我们正要出门 等一下要动一个重大手术，所以…
- Duty calls。Sorry。- I've got to prep.
- 有责任在身，抱歉 - 我得去做准备
Scrub up.
我要去消毒
- Bye-bye。- Bye.
- 再见 - 再见
See you in a minute.
待会见
It's just a tiny emergency。Make yourself at home.
小事一桩，你在家里等我
We'll talk later。Go save lives.
待会再聊，我得去救人一命
Love you.
爱你
Head of gynecology？
妇产科负责人？
Wait a second.
等一下
Bos？There's a waxer on your 6.
老波？ 你的六点钟方向有个涂蜡手？
Is that you，Lord？
是您在说话吗？上帝
Get in there and see if he uses pineapple Sex Wax.
去看看他是否用菠萝防滑蜡
Dylan，check it out.
黛伦，看吧
I got sand in my ass。I can't hardly walk.
沙子卡在我的屁股里 我根本走不动
Just blend in。Be cool，Bos.
快混过去，装做酷一点，老波
Got any wax？
你有蜡吗？
Great job，Bos.
做得好，老波
Is that grape？It's grape.
是葡萄口味吗？是葡萄口味
It's grape！
是葡萄口味
Yes，sir！
没错
Suspect four eliminated.
排除四号嫌犯
What's up，Angel？
还好吧？娇娃
- Madison Lee？- Natalie Cook？
- 麦迪逊·李 - 娜塔丽·库克
Oh，my God.
天啊
How did you know？
你怎么知道？
- I get the newsletter。- Of course.
- 我有订通讯报 - 当然
Wow。I've heard so many stories about you。You're my favorite Angel.
我听说很多你的伟大故事 你是我最喜欢的娇娃
She won the Nobel Prize for her research on flying mammals.
她研究飞行哺乳动物 得到诺贝尔奖
And predicted Carmine DeSoto's every move…
利用《Cosmo》床边占星专栏
by using the Cosmo Bedside Astrologer.
预测卡曼迪索托的一举一动
I also set the clock on Charlie's VCR.
我还帮查理设定录像机的时间
And she invented the molar mike.
她发明了迫击炮牛奶
- Dylan and Alex？- Yeah.
- 黛伦与艾丽斯？ - 对
- God，how I miss stakeouts。- I know。Aren't they the best？
- 天啊，我超怀念监视行动的 - 我知道，它们是最棒的吧？
Bring it on Bitch！
放马过来，混蛋
Only one waxer left.
只剩下一名涂蜡手
Wait a second.
等一下
Subpatellar scar，left knee.
髌下伤疤，左膝
Check it out。Brown shorts，red board，11 o'clock。What do you think？
看一下，棕短裤，红色冲浪板 11点钟方向，你觉得呢？
- Yummy。- That's what I thought.
- 很可口 - 我也那么想
Case closed。Nat，move in。Dylan thinks he's hot.
破案了，小娜，展开行动 黛伦觉得他很帅
What do you mean？
你是什么意思？
You always fall for the bad guy.
你老是爱上坏男人
Then this guy must be really evil.
这家伙应该是超邪恶的
You should see the new agency。It's beautiful.
你该到新办公室看看，真的很漂亮
Maybe I will。Tell Charlie hello for me when you see him.
或许我会的 见到查理时，帮我跟他问好
You know.
你知道的
There she goes.
她走了
Who do you think will be the first of us to leave？
你觉得我们之中谁会先离开？
You，me or Natalie？
你、我或娜塔丽？
- What are you talking about？- I think it'll be Nat.
- 你在胡说什么？ - 我想一定是小娜
Why？Did she say something？
为什么？她说了什么吗？
Nat and Pete live together now。Soon they'll be engaged…
小娜跟彼特住在一起 很快他们会订婚
…and you and I will wear pink dresses…
你跟我得穿上粉红色伴娘服
…at the wedding of Mr。and Mrs。Pete Kominsky.
参加彼特·康明斯基夫妇的婚礼
Yeah，but even if she got married，she'd never leave us.
对，可是就算她结婚了 她也不会离开我们
Sooner or later，you and I are gonna have to break in a new Angel.
迟早你和我得跟新娇娃搭档
Good morning，Angels.
早安，娇娃们
Good morning，Charlie.
早安，查理
- Good morning，Angels。- Good morning，Charlie.
- 早安，娇娃们 - 早安，查理
Good morning，Angels.
早安，娇娃们
Good morning，Charlie.
早安，查理
I mean，you didn't think it would be the three of us forever，did you？
你该不会以为 我们三个会永远搭档下去吧？
I think I lost my nuts。Your nuts ever get small？
我摸不到我的蛋蛋 你的蛋蛋会变小吗？
When I get in water，they just shrink up。They become like one marble.
我一下水，蛋蛋就会缩小 变得跟弹珠差不多
Killer，huh？
很讨厌吧？
I just got so excited.
我真的好兴奋
When it's big like that，I love to ride it hard and rough.
它那么大时，我喜欢来点猛的
Sorry.
抱歉
The way I was getting pounded，I'm gonna be wet for hours.
我老是被泡，得在水里待个几小时
Catch you later.
待会见
Randy Emmers.
兰迪·艾莫斯
- Pineapple Sex Wax。- 「The Coal Bowl.」
- 菠萝防滑蜡 - “煤坑赛道”
Hey，check it out，「Leo」，that could be his next target.
看吧，“李欧” 那应该是他的下一个目标
This is it.
过去瞧瞧吧
The Coal Bowl.
煤坑赛道
Let's get dirty.
我们该大玩一场
- I'll buy in。- I'll find Leo.
- 我去报名 - 我找李欧
I'll look for Emmers.
我去找艾莫斯
- I'll look for Emmers。- Yeah.
- 我去找艾莫斯 - 对
All right，Leo，you're mine.
好吧，李欧，你是我的了
Good luck.
祝你好运
- You in charge here？- You know it.
- 你是负责人？ - 没错
- I want in。- It's a two-G buy-in。Winner takes all.
- 我要报名 - 报名费两千块，赢家通杀
- Rules are，there are no rules。- I'm down.
- 规则是没有规则 - 我接受
Three out of four don't cross the finish line.
四分之三的人到不了终点
I'll take those odds.
我愿意冒险
Hey，how's it going？
怎么样？
- Metzger's at the far double。- Is this your first time？
- 梅兹杰在对面的双环区 - 这是你第一次…
Carmichael's at the finish line.
卡麦克在终点
I was thinking may…
我想或…
You and Pete moving in together is a big deal.
你跟彼特住在一起是很重要的事
- Yeah，it's great，isn't it？- So where do you see this going？
- 对，那真的很棒吧？ - 你觉得未来呢？
Going？I'm confused.
未来？我不懂
Okay，say someone was to come up to me and say：
好吧，假设有人跑来跟我说
「Hey，Dylan，do you think Natalie wants to get married？」
“黛伦，你觉得娜塔丽想结婚吗？”
What？Did Pete ask you to ask me if I wanted to get married？
什么？彼特要你来问我 我想不想结婚吗？
- No。- Because we just moved in together.
- 不 - 我们才刚刚住在一起
Heads up，I've spotted Emmers。I'm on him.
等一下，我看到艾莫斯了 我要去盯他
Red bike，red helmet.
红色摩托车，红色安全帽
Nat，number 25。Check it out.
小娜，25号，看吧
The lion。That's Leo.
狮子，他就是李欧
I got it。The guy in blue.
我看到了，穿蓝衣的家伙
I got shut out.
我被挡开了
- What was that？- He's after Leo.
- 那是怎么一回事？ - 他在追杀李欧
He just took out a guy in the front double.
他在前双环区撂倒一个家伙
- He's making his way up to Leo。- I'm gonna get him.
- 他要去追李欧 - 我得去追他
That's it！Let's get in there.
够了，轮到我们上场
I got him，I got him！
我看到他了
- He's gonna crush him！- Look out，Nat！
- 他要撞倒他 - 小心，小娜
What the hell are you doing？！
你到底在做什么？
Nat，he's on your 6.
小娜，他在你的六点钟方向
No，Natalie！
不，娜塔丽
- Natalie！- I'm okay.
- 娜塔丽 - 我没事
We gotta take him out！
我们得把他解决掉
I'll get back in.
我会立刻跟上去
Let's go！
走吧
Get him at the double.
在双环区解决他
- You okay？- Yeah.
- 你没事吧？ - 没事
Hey，what are you doing with my bike？
你干嘛抢我的摩托车？
Dylan！
黛伦
The Thin Man.
瘦皮猴
He's dead.
他死了
- What the hell is going on？- Hey，you're just a kid.
- 到底发生了什么事？ - 你只是一个小孩子
I'm 15 and a half.
我15岁半了
Photos。Alan Caufield.
照片，亚伦·考菲德
- Max Petroni。- How'd you know my real name？
- 麦斯·佩托尼 - 你怎么知道我的真名？
What the hell's this？
这是怎么一回事？
Hey，this is a picture of Dylan.
这是黛伦的照片
The name on the back is Helen Zaas.
后面写着“海伦·萨斯”
Helen Zaas.
海伦·萨斯
My name before I went into…
那是我的真名，直到…
…the Witness Protection Program 8 years ago.
八年前我加入证人保护计划
And then I became Dylan Sanders.
后来我成为黛伦·桑德斯
When the FBI realized the young lady's potential…
联邦调查局发现这个女孩有潜力
…they gave me a call.
他们打电话给我
- Okay，wait。Helen Zaas？- Yeah.
- 好吧，等一下，海伦·萨斯？ - 对
- That's your name？- Yeah.
- 那你的本名？ - 对
Helen Zaas.
海伦·萨斯
So where does that name come from originally？Is that Ass-tralian？
那是哪门子的鬼名字？ 你祖辈是“澳洲屁民”吗？
Yeah.
对
Oh，my God，you must have been the butt of every joke.
天啊，你一定常被取笑
- Did you drive an Aston Martin？- Alex，we're being asinine.
- 你以前开“小屁车”吗？ - 艾丽斯，我们在说什么“屁话”？
Yes，you are.
没错
Don't worry，Dylan。We're still gonna be your best butties.
别担心，黛伦 我们永远都会是你最好的“跟屁虫”
Now，Angels，a rose by any other name still smells as sweet.
好了，娇娃 玫瑰不论叫什么名字都一样芳香
Thank you，Charlie。It's not that funny.
谢谢你，查理，那一点都不好笑
Yeah，it is.
不，很好笑
- Bos，can I get a ruling on this one？- You sure can.
- 老波，能请你评评理吗？ - 当然可以
You know what？Personally，I'm not interested in Helen Zaas.
你知道吗？ 我个人对海伦·萨斯没兴趣
I'm more concerned about yours.
我比较关心你
No matter what，you're still gonna be our Dylan.
不论如何，你都是我们的黛伦
- Thank you，Bos。- You're welcome.
- 谢谢你，老波 - 不客气
Let me guess，you fell for the bad guy.
让我猜猜，你爱上坏男人
I fell for the worst guy.
我爱上超级大坏蛋
But he was so cute，and I liked him so much.
但他真的好可爱，我非常喜欢他
We had so much fun together…
我们在一起非常开心
…just driving around，listening to metal and…
开车兜风，听重金属音乐
（八年前）
And then one night，things got really bad.
某晚一切都变了
I love you！I would die for you，Seamus！
我爱你 我愿意为你而死，西慕斯
O'Grady.
欧葛莱帝
You got some balls.
你真的很有种
He said he'd kill me if I told anyone，but I had to put him away.
他说我要是敢说出去，他就会杀了我 但我必须检举他
- Of course you did。- You did the right thing.
- 当然你得那么做 - 你做了正确决定
- He was my first。- Really？
- 他是我的第一次 - 真的吗？
- But you told me you never did it。- My first bust.
- 但你跟我说你从没做过 - 我第一次抓人
- Yeah。- Who was this guy？
- 对 - 这家伙到底是谁？
- Seamus O'Grady。- O'Grady？
- 西慕斯·欧葛莱帝 - 欧葛莱帝？
- As in the Irish mob？- I sent him to prison.
- 那个爱尔兰黑帮份子？ - 我送他去坐牢
（现在）
O'Grady.
欧葛莱帝
You're out.
你可以出狱了
（只有上帝能审判我）
O'Grady，what about your belongings？
欧葛莱帝，你的东西呢？
So if I have these，she'll find me？
只要我拿到这些，她会来找我？
- The O'Gradys killed my parents。- What？
- 欧葛莱帝帮杀了我爸妈 - 什么？
Sorry，Max.
抱歉，麦斯
I testified against them.
我作证指控他们
Wait a second。Alan Caufield。He testified against the O'Gradys.
等一下，亚伦·考菲德 他作证指控欧葛莱帝帮
That's it。The O'Gradys must have HALO。This is our one lead.
这就对了，欧葛莱帝帮一定拿到 幻影清单了，这是我们唯一的线索
The Thin Man.
瘦皮猴
- Our favorite assassin。- That's right.
- 我们最爱的杀手 - 没错
- This needs to go get analyzed。- Yes，let's get up in there and do that.
- 这需要加以分析 - 对，我们得送到实验室做分析
Let me see it.
让我看一下
Yeah，I know exactly what this is。I have one.
对，我知道它是什么，我也有一个
The nuns gave it to us at the orphanage.
孤儿院的修女给我们的
Orphanage.
孤儿院
- Good work。- Max is in our protective custody now.
- 做得好 - 现在我们得保护麦斯
- It's up to us to keep him safe。- Hey，I know the safest place in town.
- 我们必须保护他的安全 - 我知道城里最安全的地方
Listen，don't you worry about a thing.
听着，不用担心
No O'Grady ever set foot in South Central。Can you dig it？
欧葛莱帝帮的人不会到中南区 你懂吗？
- Yeah。- This is my mama house.
- 对 - 这是我妈家
Rule number one：Don't look her in the eye。Understand？
第一点，别看着她的眼睛，懂吗？
Or she'll pop。Can you dig it？
不然她会抓狂的，你了解吗？
- Bosley。- Yes，ma'am？
- 波西 - 是的
You get over here.
给我过来
Hey，Mama.
妈妈
- What kind of trouble you in now？- I'm not in any trou… Yes，ma'am.
- 你又惹上什么麻烦了？ - 我没有惹…好的
- Come on。- Yes，ma'am.
- 来吧 - 好的
- Look at those knockers。- Boys！
- 看看那些门环 - 孩子们
Mother superior will see you now.
院长可以见你们了
Mother，do you recognize this man？
院长，你认得这个人吗？
Of course I know who he is.
我当然知道他是谁
We called him Anthony，after St。Anthony of Padua…
我们以圣安东尼之名 为他取名为安东尼
…healer of the mute。Please come forward.
哑巴的治疗者，请前面一点
Please，girls.
拜托，女孩们
But his real name，like so much about him，was a mystery.
但他的真名跟他的身分一样是个谜
He came to us when he was 7.
他七岁时到这里来
He was found wandering in the hills，living off roots and insects.
有人发现他在山丘游荡 靠吃树根与昆虫维生
We believe his family was in a Romanian circus troupe…
我们相信他的家人 是罗马尼亚巡演马戏团
…who died in a terrible fire.
他们死于一场大火中
Although the doctors could find nothing physically wrong…
医生发现他的健康没问题
…he never spoke a word.
但他一句话都不说
And there were other idiosyncrasies。He was a painfully shy child…
除了其他的特质 他是个非常害羞的孩子
…until it came time for his monthly haircut.
直到有一次他的剪头时间
Then one morning，he was simply gone.
有天早上他走了
The Thin Man was protecting Max.
瘦皮猴在保护麦斯
So you're saying this man is the sole benefactor of your orphanage？
你说这个人是孤儿院 唯一的捐款人？
Yes，he really is an angel.
对，他真的是个天使
Mother，have you had contact with him since？
院长，之后你跟他有联络吗？
Well，not really that much…
我们不常联络
…except for the odd haircut now and then.
他偶尔会来剪头发
But he does send gifts。Like this morning.
但他会送礼物过来，譬如今天早上
- Emmers' car。- That is a nice ride.
- 艾莫斯的车 - 这辆车很不错
An original 1967 numbers-matching GTO.
1967年份的同名车牌跑车
- Thorn Birds。- I know.
- 刺鸟 - 我知道
Bird poo.
鸟屎
What order did you girls say you were from again？
你们说你们来自哪个教会？
- Larus californicus。- California gull.
- 加州海鸥 - 加州海鸥
Fecal matter consists mostly of scaly clypeiform.
粪便主要成份是罕见圆盾物质
Sardines that fed on large brown algae，I'd say.
我相信沙丁鱼吃大量棕藻
There's also traces of tanker fuel and storm-water runoff as well.
还有坦克油料残余物 跟暴风雨洪水
Sea gulls，tankers，storm water.
海鸥、坦克、暴风雨
San Pedro Harbor.
圣彼得港
- Who are you？- What？！Wait.
- 你是谁？ - 什么？等一下
- What？- Who are you？
- 什么？ - 你是谁？
Oh，Jason Gibbons.
杰森·吉邦斯
The actor.
我是演员
Maybe you've seen Maximum Extreme.
或许你看过《极限》
No.
没看过
- It was such a big movie。- What are you doing here？
- 那是部卖座片 - 你来这里做什么？
- I'm Alex's boyfriend。- Alex's boyfriend.
- 我是艾丽斯的男朋友 - 艾丽斯的男朋友
Yeah。Well，technically，we're on what she calls a time-out.
对，技术上来说 我们处于她所谓的冷静期
- What does that mean？- Exactly。Thank you.
- 那是什么意思？ - 没错，谢谢你
Yeah。I gotta say，you must be the world's most understanding father.
对，我得说你是全世界 最了解状况的爸爸
- Why？- All the wild stuff she does.
- 为什么？ - 她做的那些疯狂事情
When I first met Alex，I thought she was a bikini waxer.
我刚认识艾丽斯时 以为她是除毛美容师
It was months before I knew about Charlie.
那是我知道查理几个月前的事
Who's Charlie？
查理又是谁？
（圣彼得港）
（梅金号，都柏林）
Merkin.
梅金号
That was the name of Seamus' pit bull.
跟西慕斯养的斗牛犬同名
Armed guards。Security looks pretty tight.
武装警卫，戒备蛮森严的
This dock is like a fortress.
这座码头跟碉堡差不多
ID badges。I think cargo's our best bet.
通行证 我想货柜装了我们要找的东西
- Townsend Agency。- Bos，recon incoming.
- 汤森侦探社 - 老波，侦搜资料正在传送中
- Got you，baby。- Yeah，check the photo.
- 收到了，宝贝 - 对，看一下照片
（货柜）
That's our man.
那是我们要找的
（藏宝箱）
The Treasure Chest.
藏宝箱
- Do a little dance。- Make a little love.
- 跳跳舞 - 放纵一下
Get down tonight.
今晚要玩到趴下
- There he is，first table on the right。- Yeah，baby！
- 他在那边，右边第一桌 - 太棒了，宝贝
Hold.
等一下
（港务局码头部，派帝·欧迈利）
- Paddy O'Malley？- Top of the morning to you.
- 派帝·欧迈利？ - 早安
You know，you just don't look much like any Paddy I've ever seen before.
你长得不像我认识的欧迈利
Ain't never heard of no black Irish？
你不认识爱尔兰黑人吗？
- Black Irish？- That's right.
- 爱尔兰黑人？ - 没错
Who do you think invented the McRib，Lucky Charms，huh？
你以为谁发明了肋排跟幸运符？
- Shamrock Shake？That's ours。- Give me your papers.
- 酢浆草奶昔？那是我们的点子 - 请出示文件
- What？- Your papers.
- 什么？ - 你的文件
Let me tell you…
我得告诉你
…you got nerve to ask me about my papers.
别跟我要文件
My family suffered，man，for lack of potatoes.
我家人因为没马铃薯吃而受苦
Foot-and-mouth disease。Canker sores。Circumcision.
还有口蹄疫、口腔溃疡跟割礼
- Circumcision？- Right，my wife just had a set of twins.
- 割礼？ - 对，我太太刚生了一对双胞胎
- Both leprechauns。- Leprechauns？
- 两个都是小妖精 - 小妖精？
Get a whiff。Irish Spring.
闻一下，爱尔兰春天
You don't believe that，wipe your ass with a four-leaf clover.
你不会相信的 拿四叶苜蓿草来擦屁股
McGinty！
麦金提
Get this stuff on the ship.
把东西搬到船上
- Tough，eh？- That was heavy.
- 很辛苦吧？ - 那真的是超重的
I say we should take a break.
我想我们该休息一下
Wait a second.
等一下
I smell a rat.
我闻到老鼠味
This ring is pure platinum.
这戒指是纯铂金所制
The HALO rings are titanium.
幻影戒指是钦做的
HALO data chips should be weightless…
幻影资料晶片应该没重量
…surrounded by a hollow core that prevents thermal induction.
包在中空核心里，避免热能渗入
If the density of the object…
如果物质密度
…is less than that of the substance in which it is immersed…
比沉入物质的密度低
It floats.
它会浮起来
There they are.
有了
I'm sure Helen Zaas was great，but I just can't imagine life…
我相信海伦·萨斯很棒 但我无法想像
…without Dylan Sanders.
没有黛伦·桑德斯的生活
- Come on，let's get out of here。- Cheers to that.
- 来吧，我们该离开这里了 - 来为此而干一杯吧
What's the rush，Helen？
急什么，海伦？
You've only been here five minutes.
你才来五分钟
Now，I've waited for you before.
我一直在等你
Matter of fact，I've waited for you 2920 days.
事实上我等了2920天
That's 417 weeks.
等于417周
That's 96 months.
96个月
That's eight years.
八年
Enough about me.
我等得够久了
What about you，Helen？How have you been？
你呢，海伦？你还好吗？
Seamus.
西慕斯
I see you still got a nice arse on you.
看来你过得还不错
You got a lot of nerve stealing from me.
你胆子大到敢偷我的东西
- Stealing back's more like it。- Give us the rings.
- 应该说我是来把东西拿回去 - 把戒指还给我们
Give us the rings.
把戒指还给我们
Give us the rings！
Don't lose those。We'll be taking them back in about…
别把它们弄丢了 我们会把它们拿回来
…48 seconds.
再过48秒
I've been dreaming one day I'd get to see you again…
我一直梦想有一天能再见到你
…and watch you die.
看着你死掉
Keep dreaming.
继续做梦吧
Lights。Somebody get the lights！
开灯，快点开灯
Seamus.
西慕斯
Seamus！
You know I always like it with the light on.
你知道我一向喜欢开灯做
- You don't know me anymore。- I'm the only one here who knows you.
- 你不再了解我 - 我是这里唯一了解你的人
Wait，wait，wait！
等一下
I've got to say，Helen，I've never wanted you more.
海伦，我得说 我现在太想要得到你了
- Always wanting what you can't have。- Yeah？
- 你只要你得不到的东西 - 是吗？
I'll have you any way I want.
我要怎么处置你都可以
I got the rings。Let's get out of here！
我拿到戒指了，快离开这里
Don't let them get away！
别让她们跑了
Got it？
可以了吗？
Come on，now！
快来吧
Let's go.
走吧
Dylan，let's go.
黛伦，该走了
You can't hurt me anymore，Helen.
你再也无法伤害我，海伦
I'm gonna teach you and your friends about pain.
我会教你跟你朋友痛苦的滋味
I'm gonna kill them just so you can hear them scream.
我会杀了她们 让你听到她们的求救声
Dylan！
黛伦
I got the rings.
我拿到戒指了
- Are you okay？- Yeah，I'm okay.
- 你没事吧？ - 我没事
Hit it.
走吧
I know who did it.
我知道是谁干的
Hot damn it，I know who did it.
该死，我知道是谁干的
Col。Mustard，in the dining room，with a lead pipe.
芥末上校，在餐厅，拿着铅管
- Col。Mustard？- Give me that.
- 芥末上校？ - 快给我
- Col。Mustard？- I said，Col。Mustard…
- 芥末上校？ - 我说芥末上校
…in the dining room，with a lead pipe.
在餐厅，拿着铅管
- Go ahead and look in there。- Why don't you look.
- 你可以去看一下 - 你何不去看一下？
Col。Must…
芥末…
- Col。Mustard？- Right.
- 芥末上校？ - 对
Col。Mustard？Col。Mustard？
芥末上校？
It's Professor Plum…
是梅子教授
…in the conservatory，with a candlestick.
在温室，拿着蜡烛
That's right。You got it right.
没错，你答对了
- Damn！- How the hell you know that？
- 该死 - 你怎么知道？
We took in one just like him a long time ago，remember？
很久前我们买了一个，记得吗？
Yeah，Mama，I remember。You gave my room away.
对，妈妈，我记得 你把我的房间清空了
（十周年同学会，莱戴尔高中）
You were the cock？I was the beaver.
你是公鸡？我是水獭
What are the chances that we were both mascots？
机率太低了吧？我们都是吉祥物
- Unbelievable。- Oh，God.
- 不可思议 - 天啊
It's like we were made for each other.
感觉上我们是天生一对
The best I can figure it is，the clients contact Charlie directly.
就我所知，客户直接联络查理
Okay，then he phones the girls.
好吧，然后他打电话给女孩们
They show up at the place and do their thing.
她们出现在指定地点 做她们的工作
Now，I know，I know。At first，I didn't think I could handle it.
我知道 刚开始我也以为我会无法接受
The late nights，the never knowing when she'd have to go out on a job.
深夜不归，不知道何时她得去工作
Some of the men are pretty dangerous.
有些男人还蛮危险的
And the outfits。Oh，boy.
她得变装，天啊
I'll be right back，Pete。It's just number one。Have fun.
我马上回来，彼特 我只是要上一号，玩得开心点
（女厕，男厕）
Hello？
有人吗？
I'm gonna say this。Our boy Pete has no idea what he's getting into.
我得说我们的兄弟彼特 不知道他惹上什么麻烦
I don't think he really understands the responsibility.
我不认为他了解什么是责任
- No，no。- Pete？
- 没错 - 彼特？
- The commitment。- Once they get into your house…
- 承诺 - 一旦它们进了你家
- …you lose all spontaneity。- Gone.
- 你会失去所有正常生活 - 没错
They do whatever they want.
它们爱做什么，就做什么
- Pete's asking her tonight？- That's what he said.
- 今晚彼特要问她吗？ - 他是那么说的
But Alex is a wildcat.
但艾丽斯真的很野
I mean，she gives as good as she gets.
我是说她做起事来全力以赴
Alex！Hey.
艾丽斯
Jason，Daddy。What are you doing here，Jason？
杰森，爸 你在这里做什么，杰森？
I was just explaining to your father here all about Charlie.
我在跟你爸解释查理的事
Charlie？
查理？
- Daddy… - It's all right，Alex。I know.
- 爸 - 没关系，艾丽斯，我都知道了
I'm so sorry，Daddy，that I didn't tell you.
爸，我真的很抱歉没有早点告诉你
I didn't think you'd approve。I know you wanted me to be a neurosurgeon.
我觉得你不会同意 我知道你要我当神经外科医生
But I've discovered a whole new way to help people…
但我找到全新方式来帮助别人
…that makes me feel so…
那让我觉得…
…alive.
爽爆了
Whatever makes you happy.
只要你开心就好了
I am so relieved！
我真的是大大地松了一口气
It's just been killing me，you not knowing all these years。I…
我真的好难过 这些年来你一直不知情，我…
Daddy…
爸
…Natalie，Dylan and I are a team.
娜塔丽、黛伦跟我是搭档
And we just took on 12 sailors.
我们刚刚解决掉12名水手
You can't even imagine the positions we get ourselves into.
你无法想像我们的处境是怎样的
Daddy，I wish you could watch us work。You'd be so proud.
爸，真希望你能来看我们工作 你会觉得很骄傲
I'm gonna take a shower…
我要去冲个澡
…because I am covered in… Well，you can only imagine what.
因为我全身都是… 你一定无法想像的
And then when I get back，I am gonna give you…
洗完澡后，我要跟你…
…a full blow-by-blow.
好好地吹一下
Ferret.
天啊
- Natalie？- What，Pete？
- 期仔塔丽 - 什么事，彼特？
- I've been thinking。- Yeah？
- 我一直在想 - 什么？
- About what？- Well，look…
- 你在想什么？ - 听着
…I know we just moved in together.
我知道我们才刚刚住在一起
- Yeah？- Yeah.
- 对吧？ - 对
And I know we agreed to take this kind of slow.
我知道我们说好要慢慢来
- But… - Yeah？
- 可是… - 什么？
There's just something I gotta ask.
有件事我得问你
- Oh，boy。- Yeah，「Oh，boy」 is right.
- 天啊 - 对，天啊，没错
So here it goes.
我要说了
- Twirl me first。- Okay.
- 先让我转个圈 - 好的
Yeah.
对
Hey！
嘿
- About that question，Pete？- Let's talk about it later.
- 你要问我什么，彼特？ - 我们再找时间谈
（小娜与艾丽斯）
「Here's all your stuff back.」
“东西通通还给你们”
What's up with that？
那是怎么一回事？
She's gone.
她走了
She's not coming back.
她不会回来了
She loved these boots.
她爱这双靴子
She doesn't want us to get hurt.
她不希望我们受伤害
Wait a minute，you ladies risk your ass every day.
等一下，你们每天都冒着生命危险
Yeah.
对
「I'll never forgive myself if anything happens to you.」
“如果你们出了事 我永远都不会原谅自己”
Where do we go from here，Charlie？
我们该怎么办呢？查理
Natalie，Alex。You need to keep your spirits up.
娜塔丽、艾丽斯 你们得打起精神
Any leads on the O'Gradys，Charlie？
有欧葛莱帝帮的消息吗？查理
Any word on how Seamus broke out of prison？
知道西慕斯是怎么越狱的吗？
He didn't break out，Natalie。He was released.
他没有越狱，娜塔丽 他是合法出狱
What？Who would have the power to pull something like that off？
什么？谁有那么大的势力 可以那么做？
Johnnie Cochran.
强尼·柯奇朗
The Justice Department，the DA's office，the FBI.
司法部、地检署、联邦调查局
U.S。Marshal.
美国执法官
That's Carter.
卡特来了
I never gave rings to a guy before.
我不曾把戒指交给男人
The rings are secure，sir.
拿到戒指了，长官
And we can all breathe a little easier.
现在我们可以松口气了
- Well done，Angels。- Thanks，Charlie.
- 做得好，娇娃们 - 谢谢你，查理
HALO is safe，thanks to you.
幻影计划安全了，谢谢你们
It's been a pleasure.
这是我们的荣幸
I hope to work with you ladies again.
希望能再度跟你们合作
But not too soon.
最好不要太快
Good luck with everything.
祝你们好运
Your keys.
你的钥匙
- What is it？- My ribs.
- 怎么了？ - 我的肋骨
These aren't mine.
这不是我的钥匙
That was a nice reach for a guy with a couple of fractured ribs.
对一个断了几根肋骨的家伙来说 他的身手蛮敏捷的
Good going，Bos.
做得好，老波
- We got him。- We got who？
- 我们逮到他了 - 我们逮到谁了？
Of course，he already had one ring。He just needed the other.
当然，他已经有一枚戒指 他只需要另一枚戒指
He wanted to fake his own death so he wouldn't be a suspect.
他要装死，才不会变成嫌犯
Who you all talking about？
你们到底在说谁？
He needed time for his plan，so he set up Seamus.
他的计划需要时间 所以他把西慕斯当成棋子
Then turned him loose on Dylan.
要他找黛伦报仇
I think you're onto something，Angels.
我想你们找到线索了，娇娃们
Damn！So Carter's the bad guy！
该死，原来卡特是坏蛋
It's just speculation at this point，Bosley。We need proof.
现在只是推测 波西，我们需要证据
- Keys，Bosley。- Let's hit it.
- 钥匙，波西 - 该出发了
Punk.
混蛋
Road's clear。You're good to move in.
前面没人，你可以行动了
Almost there.
快好了
Oncoming.
有车接近
Good job，Alex.
做得好，艾丽斯
（停）
- Can we go yet？- No，you can't，son.
- 我们能过去了吗？ - 不，还不行，孩子
I gotta make sure it's safe.
我得确定安全
- We're gonna be late。- You're not gonna be late，young ma…
- 我们会迟到的 - 你不会迟到的，年轻人
You old grizzly bear！
你这个臭老头
Son，please work with me，young man.
孩子，请跟我合作
A few more minutes and you'll be in school。You'll never see me again.
再过几分钟，你们就会到学校 你们再也不会跟我见面
Man，you do not mess with a black man's do！
天啊，别弄乱我的头发
I got the phone line.
我接上电话线了
I'm calling from my car。Go secure.
我打车上电话，换安全路线
My end of the deal's done。The Angels are off the case.
我这边的工作都完成了 娇娃们已经退出这个案子
I have the rings.
戒指在我手上
Dylan.
黛伦
Alex！Alex！
艾丽斯
Call buyer one.
去电一号买家
Alex，are you okay？
艾丽斯，你没事吧？
Nat，the handle's broken。I can't disengage.
小娜，把手坏了，我无法脱离
The deal's on。Eight o'clock，just as we discussed.
开始交易，八点钟 跟我们说过的一样
- Nat，plan B！- I'm calling in Bosley.
- 小娜，B计划 - 我要打电话给波西
We'll get you out of there，Alex。Hang tight.
我们会帮你脱身的，艾丽斯 撑着点
Follow the stars beyond the galaxy.
在银河下跟着星星走
Take shore to hope。Stop on a stair.
登岸寻找希望，在楼梯下停住脚步
A stair？
楼梯？
Find a man with a map.
找到有地图的人
Bosley，can you hear me？
波西，你听到了吗？
Bosley，we're going to Bravo configuration immediately.
波西，我们得立刻进行B计划
I'm on it。I'm on it。Okay？
我立刻处理，好吗？
Now，get back。We're going to Bravo configuration。Get back！
退后，我们要进行B计划
Stop！
停
- Come on。- Okay。Come on，hurry.
- 来吧 - 好了，来吧，快一点
Skip。Run.
动作快，跑起来
Get on out of here.
快离开这里
Come on。Get on out of here.
来吧，快离开这里
- Great job，Bos。- Yeah，right.
- 做得好，老波 - 对
Carter's working with a partner。They're selling the list tonight.
卡特有共犯，今晚他们要卖掉清单
We'll take care of them and then find Dylan.
我们得解决他们，再去找黛伦
- See you，Bos。- Yeah，all right，all right.
- 再见，老波 - 对，好吧
This is some bullshit.
这简直是在胡闹
（墨西哥）
- Kelly Garrett。- Hello，Dylan.
- 凯莉·嘉瑞特 - 你好，黛伦
Don't you have a case to solve？
你不必去办案吗？
Well，I tried to outrun my past，but it caught up with me yesterday.
我努力要摆脱过去 昨天一切又回来了
And I put my friends in danger.
我害我的朋友置身险境
They're in more danger now without you.
现在你不在，她们更危险了
Natalie and Alex are gonna replace me with someone great.
娜塔丽跟艾丽斯 会找更棒的人来取代我
A real Angel。Not someone who's pretending to be something she's not.
一个真正的娇娃 不是一心只想假装自己能做到的人
Your past is what makes you who you are，Dylan.
你的过去造就现在的你，黛伦
Don't forget that Charlie chose you for a reason.
别忘了查理选择你是有原因的
Angels are like diamonds.
娇娃就跟钻石一样
They can't be made。You have to find them.
那是训练不来的，你得寻找她们
Each one is unique.
每一个娇娃都很独特
Sometimes we search too hard for answers that are right in front of us.
有时我们只忙着寻找 反而看不到摊在我们眼前的答案
（《时尚COSMOPOLITAN》杂志）
（床边占星专栏）
（好莱坞）
The buyers are set.
买家都到了
We did it，partner！
我们办到了，伙伴
You know，I never really got that partner thing.
我真的不喜欢跟别人搭档
Hello，Angels.
娇娃们，你们好
Madison Lee.
麦迪逊·李
Why？
为什么？
Why be an Angel when I can play God？
我可以扮演上帝 为什么要当娇娃？
Looks like one of the three amigos has gone adios.
看起来三个好朋友少了一个
Welcome back，Dylan.
欢迎你回来，黛伦
You're such a typical rebellious Pisces.
你是典型的叛逆少女
Always out to prove how tough you are…
总是要证明自己有多强
…and you couldn't make it one day on your own，could you？
你靠自己根本办不到，对吧？
Someone reminded me that every Angel is unique.
有人提醒我，每个娇娃都很独特
And I knew it was you.
我知道幕后主使就是你
Who else had contacts in Mongolia…
还有谁能在蒙古找到联络人
…could hack the HALO fail-safe and hire a surfer as an assassin？
可以打开幻影计划安全程序 雇用冲浪手当杀手？
Same astrological phenom who would refer to a motocross rider…
知道越野摩托车手 会用星座来当成代号
…with a lion on his helmet as 「Leo.」
他的安全帽有狮子图案 代表他就是李欧
Very well done.
做得好
Very impressive，really.
真的非常厉害
You've got it all figured out.
你们都弄清楚了
And now I'm gonna really enjoy…
现在我可以好好享受
…knocking those halos right off your heads.
让你们无法再思考的乐趣
But you're an Angel.
你是娇娃
No。You just don't get it.
不，你不了解
I don't take orders from a speaker box anymore.
我不再听命扩音器传来的命令
I work for myself.
我为自己工作
Well，your boss sucks.
你的老板很差劲
The Angels' ass-kicking pose.
娇娃出击姿势
Seeing the three of you like that…
看到你们三个那么做
…does give me this little twinge of nostalgia for the old days.
让我想起以前的日子
But back then，it was a little bit different.
但以前的做法稍有不同
You see，when I was an Angel…
我还是娇娃时
…we used guns.
我们会用枪
Sorry，Charlie.
抱歉，查理
Hello，Angels.
哈喽，娇娃们
Good evening，Charlie.
晚上好，查理
I love the new office.
我喜欢新办公室
Madison，is that you？Where are the Angels？
麦迪逊，是你吗？娇娃们在哪里？
I'm sure there's three more where they came from.
我相信你能找到三个新娇娃
Madison，what have you done？
麦迪逊，你到底做了什么？
We're just having a little fun。You shouldn't worry yourself，Charlie.
我们只是闹着玩，别担心，查理
You've never had trouble…
你一直都很擅长
…finding someone to give their life for you.
找人为你卖命
Hurting the Angels doesn't prove you're the best。You know that.
伤害娇娃们无法证明你是最棒的 你很清楚那一点
Do I？
是吗？
Madison，you were never able to accept that this agency…
麦迪逊，你一直没办法接受 这个侦探社
…is about teamwork。We're a family。We do…
要求团队合作 我们是一家人，我们…
Yeah，yeah，yeah，I know。Angels forever.
对，我知道，娇娃永远是娇娃
I've heard the sales pitch.
我听过那套宣传台词
It was very seductive…
它非常有说服力
…once.
以前是的
Madison，you deliberately went rogue on the DeSoto case…
麦迪逊，你故意搞砸迪索托案
…and put your fellow Angels in danger.
害你的搭档娇娃 陷入危险的处境
When we finally got you out of there…
我们终于把你救出来时
…you were wounded so badly，we thought we might lose you.
你伤得非常重，我们以为会失去你
You did lose me.
你的确失去了我
You see，being an Angel wasn't fulfilling my destiny.
你知道的，我不适合当娇娃
It was keeping me from it.
那害我没办法做我想做的事
Your destiny is yet to be written.
你的命运还没有决定
Do not do this，Madison.
别这么做，麦迪逊
Taking the lives of innocent people is not the answer.
杀害无辜的人不是你要的答案
There must be something in you that's still good.
你一定还有善良的一面
I was never good.
我一直不是好人
I was great.
但我非常伟大
Damn。What a bitch！
该死，真是个混蛋
You guys，we have to outthink Madison.
各位，我们得跟麦迪逊斗智
No matter what we do，she's always two steps ahead of us.
不论我们怎么做 她总是能超前我们两步
- She's selling the list off tonight，8：00。- But where？
- 今晚八点她要卖掉清单 - 交易地点在哪里？
- Nat，what else did Carter say？- Okay.
- 小娜，卡特还说了什么？ - 好吧
「Take the stars beyond the galaxy.」
“在银河下跟着星星走”
It's safe to say it's on this planet.
我想交易地点应该在地球上
「Take shore to hope and stop on a stair.」
“登岸寻找希望 在楼梯下停住脚步”
- There's a Hope Street downtown。- But no shore for miles.
- 市区有一条希望街 - 但离岸边有数英里远
A stair.
楼梯
Astaire！
亚斯坦
Astaire？
亚斯坦？
Astaire！
亚斯坦
- Possible concussion。- I'm worried.
- 可能是脑震荡 - 我很担心
Guys，the stars。Hollywood Walk of Fame.
两位，星星，好莱坞星光大道
Beyond the Galaxy Theatre.
就在银河电影院再过去一点
There's Dinah Shore，Bob Hope and Fred Astaire.
有黛娜·萧、鲍勃·霍伯跟佛雷·亚斯坦
- Nice，Nat。- Yeah！
- 太棒了，小娜 - 对
I think she's trying to kill us.
我想她真的要杀了我们
（杰森·吉邦斯 《极限2》）
I can't believe it。We are here in Hollywood.
我不敢相信 我们真的在好莱坞
- Angels？- I knew we were gonna do it…
- 娇娃们 - 我知道我们得这么做
- Shut up，damn it！- What？
- 闭嘴，该死 - 什么？
I mean，not you，Mama。Sorry.
我不是说你，妈妈，对不起
- Have you lost your mind？- Yeah。I mean，no.
- 你疯了吗？ - 对，我是说不对
We gonna talk about this later.
我们待会再谈
（佛雷·亚斯坦）
（好莱坞吉尼斯世界纪录博物馆）
（迪亚伯洛集团）
（田中组）
（安东尼奥尼黑帮家族）
- Welcome to the Guinness World of… - Shut it.
- 欢迎光临吉尼斯世界… - 闭嘴
Give us the map.
给我们地图
（莫索与法兰克烧烤店）
（罗斯福饭店）
Yahtzee！
天啊
Jason！Jason！
杰森
Jason！
I love you！
我爱你
- I hear the sequel's insane。- First one was a classic.
- 听说续集很疯狂 - 第一集是经典名片
Button your jacket.
把外套扣好
- What？- Button your jacket.
- 什么？ - 把外套扣好
（罗斯福饭店）
The VIP gathering is on the top floor.
贵宾会议室在顶楼
（屋顶入口）
You're under arrest for conspiracy to obstruct justice.
你们因为阴谋妨碍司法被捕
Freeze！
不要动
（洛杉矶剧院）
The Kleinhardt gambit.
易容术
- Classic。- And apparently still effective.
- 太聪明了 - 还是有效
We never used to wear Kevlar till I took three in the chest.
直到我胸口中了三枪 我们才开始穿防弹背心
On the DeSoto case！We know！
在迪索托案，我们知道
Don't tell me you forgot about…
别告诉我，你们忘了…
…plan B.
B计划
I'd recognize that arse anywhere，you piece of sh…
我走到哪里都认得那女人，混蛋
Bring it on，bitch.
放马过来，王八蛋
Say something.
快说句话
Mind if I cut in？
我能插队吗？
No！
不行
The premiere should be a blast.
首映会应该要有爆点
Bosley，plan B！
波西，B计划
It's raining white women！
白人女性从天而降
Plan B stands for 「plan Bosley.」
B计划就是波西计划
Yeah！
太棒了
Get that bitch！Get that bitch！
逮住那个臭女人
Wow。They really went all out for this thing。Okay！
他们真的很用心办活动，好吧
Dylan！
黛伦
Alex！
艾丽斯
This is it。You ready？
就是现在，你准备好了吗？
Are you？
你呢？
Kill…
不杀人
…or be killed.
就会被杀
Exciting，isn't it？
这真的很刺激，对吧？
Who are you？
你是谁？
You want to know who I am，Natalie？
你想知道我是谁吗，娜塔丽？
Then you look inside your own heart.
你得步扪心自问
No，Madison.
不，麦迪逊
I'm nothing like you.
我跟你不一样
I have something you'll never have.
我有你没有的东西
And what's that？
什么东西？
Friends.
朋友
- Enjoy heaven。- Go to hell.
- 上天堂去吧 - 下地狱去吧
She is so fired.
她这回真的被炒了
Party time.
庆祝时间
- Angels！- Bosley！
- 娇娃们 - 波西
Angels！
娇娃们
- You all get that squirrel-flying lady？- Yeah！
- 你们解决掉飞天松鼠女了？ - 没错
- Did you scratch her？- Yeah！
- 你们有痛扁她吗？ - 对
You kick her？You kicked her kung fu ass？Mama，I told you！
你们有踢她吗？用功夫踢她？ 妈妈，我说的没错
I know it！
我知道
- We couldn't have done it without you。- Never！
- 没有你，我们是办不到的 - 没错
- You hear that，Mama？- I heard it.
- 你听到了吗？妈妈 - 我听到了
I've always known my baby boy was a genius！
我一直都知道我儿子是天才
Why you give my room away，then，Mama？
为什么你要把我的房间清空？妈妈
I'll tell you why。Max？
我来告诉你为什么，麦斯？
Yeah？I'm a Bosley now！
什么事？现在我是波西家的一份子
- Max Bosley！- I love Max Bosley！
- 麦斯·波西 - 我爱麦斯·波西
- Boy，you did it！- Hallelujah！
- 天啊，你办到了 - 哈里路亚
Daddy！One second。Daddy！
爸爸，等一下
Darling！You made it！
亲爱的，你来了
We just got done。Another satisfied client.
我们刚刚下班 又是一个非常满意的客户
We finished her off sooner than we thought.
我们解决掉她，比预期中还快
- Her？- It was a woman this time.
- 她？ - 这次是女的
We had to triple-team her，but we finally got her on her back！
我们得三人合作对付她 但终于把她搞定了
Well done！
做得好
No，no，no！
不
- Jason！- Alex。You made it.
- 杰森 - 艾丽斯，你来了
No，no，no！I know。We're on a time-out，I know.
不，我知道，我们在冷静期
Time-out's over，baby。We're back in the game！
冷静期过去了，宝贝 我们可以继续打得火热
Ferret.
天啊
I know you wanted to wait and everything，but…
我知道你想等，可是…
- You really look beautiful。- Thanks，Pete.
- 你看起来真的好漂亮 - 谢谢你，彼特
I've been wanting to ask you this for a long time.
我一直都想问你这个问题
So here goes.
我要说了
Pete.
彼特
（史派克）
- Spike？- Yeah。A puppy.
- 史派克？ - 对，小狗
A puppy？
小狗？
- Is that okay？I know it's a big step。- Yes！
- 可以吗？我知道这是一大步 - 太棒了
I already got him.
我已经把它带回家了
- You did？- Yeah.
- 是吗？ - 对
Dylan！Dylan！
黛伦
Guess what.
你猜怎么了？
Pete and I have something to tell you.
彼特跟我有事要告诉你
- Really？- We're gonna get…
- 真的吗？ - 我们要…
- You're gonna get what？- A puppy！
- 你们要做什么？ - 养小狗
- A puppy！That's great！- Yes.
- 养小狗，太棒了 - 对
- I already got him。- You did.
- 我已经把它带回家了 - 真的？
- Awesome！- His name is Spike！
- 太棒了 - 它叫史派克
- So you're not leaving？- No！Of course，you guys.
- 你不会离开？ - 当然不会，别傻了
I get to kick butt with my two best friends。You think I'd give that up？
我要跟我的两个好朋友一起抓坏蛋 你以为我会放弃吗？
No！
不
What about you，Dylan？
你呢？黛伦
With O'Grady out，you can go back to your old life.
解决掉欧葛莱帝后 你可以恢复以前的生活
Are you kidding？This is my life.
你在开玩笑吗？这就是我的生活
- What about you，neurosurgeon？- It's a no-brainer！
- 你呢？神经外科医生 - 答案太简单了
I love our family！
我爱我们这一家
God！
天啊
And I know we agreed to take things slow.
我知道我们说好要慢慢来
- Yeah？- But…
- 所以呢？ - 可是…
- You… - Sorry.
- 你… - 抱歉
There's an ember in my ass.
有余烬跑到我的屁股里
We should get this to the lab and analyze it.
我们该把这个送到实验室做分析
Yeah，just crawl right up in there.
对，爬到上面去
I have.
我是的
I like the patch.
我喜欢这个补丁
Let me see your patch.
让我看看你的补丁
Hello？
喂？
Is this Natalie？
娜塔丽在吗？
Okay！
好吧
I'm on fire！
我着火了
Look around.
看一下四周
Over your right shoulder.
看一下右后方
Is somebody coming up behind me？
有人从后面接近我吗？
I am getting pelted.
我被摔了出去
Pelted by the…
我被摔了出去，因为…
- I literally… - I have it in…
- 我真的… - 我觉得…